<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Henry Leung</title>
    <link>https://henrysky.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Henry Leung</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://henrysky.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/photography/</guid>
      <description>I like astrophotography, here are some of my works done at different places around the globe. Most of them are captured with Skywatcher 80ED on Star Adventurer equatorial mount with a modified Canon 600D.
Some of the best stargazing place I have been include Mount Everest Base Camp at 5400m above sea level and Uluru, Australia
M42 Orion Nebula 8 Nov 2015, Home at Downtown Toronto
Startrails over University College at UofT 18-19 March 2016, Front Campus at U of Toronto</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codes</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/codes/</guid>
      <description>I release most of my code including code for my papers on my Github profile
astroNN Deep Learning for Astronomers with Tensorflow
astroNN Github: https://github.com/henrysky/astroNN
mw_plot A handy python package to do plotting on a face-on/edge-on/allsky map milkyway with matplotlib and bokeh
mw_plot Github: https://github.com/henrysky/milkyway_plot
Galaxy10 A CIFAR10-like galaxy image dataset
Galaxy10 Github: https://github.com/henrysky/Galaxy10
galpy_cuda_demo Technology demonstration of orbits integration with CUDA for galpy
galpy_cuda_demo Github: https://github.com/henrysky/galpy_cuda_demo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>My current research focuses on using new robust machine learning methodology to analyze big astronomical survey data-sets, such as spectroscopic data from the Sloan Apache Point Observatory Galaxy Evolution Experiment (APOGEE) and Gaia astrometric data to better understand the Milky Way Galaxy. I use new robust machine learning methodologies such as multi-layer (&#34;deep&#34;) Bayesian artificial neural networks, which can learn complex mapping functions between inputs andoutputs while considering uncertainty in training data and also providing uncertainty estimates for predicted values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/publication/</guid>
      <description>You can view the list of my papers on SAO/NASA Astrophysics Data System 2023MNRAS.526.1997P 0 Citations Code Decoding the age-chemical structure of the Milky Way disc: an application of copulas and elicitable mapsAarya A. Patil, Jo Bovy, Sebastian Jaimungal, Neige Frankel, Henry W. Leung 2023MNRAS.tmp.2896L 4 Citations Code Towards an astronomical foundation model for stars with a Transformer-based modelHenry W. Leung, Jo Bovy 2023MNRAS.522.4577L 8 Citations Code A variational encoder-decoder approach to precise spectroscopic age estimation for large Galactic surveysHenry W.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>My LinkedIn profile: Curriculum Vitae in PDF format is available on request
Education: PhD, University of Toronto (2020-Ongoing)
MSc, University of Toronto (2019-2020)
BSc, University of Toronto (2014-2019)
Hong Kong Diploma of Secondary Education (2008-2014)
Research/Teaching: 2019 Fall: Teaching Assistant for AST101H1: The Sun and Its Neighbours
2019-2023 Summer/Winter: Teaching Assistant for AST201H1: Stars and Galaxies
2022-2023: Teaching Assistant for AST251: Life on Other Worlds
2020-2021: Teaching Assistant for AST325/326: Practical Astronomy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2023-01-19-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2023-01-19-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I was looking into how blogging is done with Github Page with Jekyll and come across a nice one developed by https://gaohaoyang.github.io/ and https://tomoya92.github.io/ which this blog is based on. While making new post which is written in markdown is straight-forward, local development such as testing after you modified the code is not easy. Mainly due to Jekyll requires Ruby which requires MSYS2 which personally dislike.
So I use Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) which is already installed on my Windows to do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogging with Jekyll and Developing it on Windows</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2019-10-14-blogging-with-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2019-10-14-blogging-with-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I was looking into how blogging is done with Github Page with Jekyll and come across a nice one developed by https://gaohaoyang.github.io/ and https://tomoya92.github.io/ which this blog is based on. While making new post which is written in markdown is straight-forward, local development such as testing after you modified the code is not easy. Mainly due to Jekyll requires Ruby which requires MSYS2 which personally dislike.
So I use Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) which is already installed on my Windows to do the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re up and running!</title>
      <link>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2014-3-3-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://henrysky.github.io/blog/2014-3-3-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>test testing testing
Next you can update your site name, avatar and other options using the _config.yml file in the root of your repository (shown below).
![_config.yml]({{ site.baseurl }}/images/config.png)
The easiest way to make your first post is to edit this one. Go into /_posts/ and update the Hello World markdown file. For more instructions head over to the Jekyll Now repository on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
